Guide to the New World Writing Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1952-1960; Series I; 8.6; (21 boxes)
  - Literary Correspondence, 1952-1959
    - Logan, John (Issues #9 and #11), circa 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 286)
    - Loos, André L. (Issue #15), circa 1959 (Box 11, Folder 287)
    - Lorca, Federico García (Issue #2), circa 1952 (Box 11, Folder 288)
    - Lowry, Malcolm (Issue #3), circa 1953 (Box 11, Folder 289)
    - Lundkvist, Arthur (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 11, Folder 290)
    - Lynds, Dennis (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 11, Folder 291)
    - McAllister, Claire (Issue #12), circa 1957 (Box 11, Folder 292)
    - Macauley, Robie (Issue #1), circa 1952 (Box 11, Folder 293)
    - MacDonagh, Donagh (Issue #4), circa 1953 (Box 11, Folder 294)
    - MacDonogh, Patrick (Issue #4), circa 1953 (Box 11, Folder 295)
    - McFadden, Roy (Issue #4), circa 1953 (Box 11, Folder 296)
    - Mairi, McInnes (Mrs. J. McCormick) (Issue #7), circa 1955 (Box 11, Folder 297)
    - Madge, Charles (Issue #12), circa 1957 (Box 11, Folder 298)
    - Magalhães, Raimundo, Jr. (Issue #7), circa 1955 (Box 11, Folder 299)
    - Mailer, Norman (Issue #2), circa 1952 (Box 12, Folder 300)
    - Makal, Mahmut (Issue #6), circa 1954 (Box 12, Folder 301)
    - Marberry, M. Marion (Issue #8), circa 1955 (Box 12, Folder 302)
    - Marcus, David (Issue #7), circa 1955 (Box 12, Folder 303)
    - Martinson, Harry (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 12, Folder 304)
    - Matchett, William H. (Issues #3 and #9), circa 1953, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 305)
    - Matson, Peter (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 12, Folder 306)
    - Matthews, T. S. (Thomas Stanley) (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 12, Folder 307)
    - Mattheissen, Peter (Issue #3), circa 1953 (Box 12, Folder 308)
    - Mayhall, Jane (Issue #2), circa 1952 (Box 12, Folder 309)
    - Mead, Margaret (Issue #3), circa 1953 (Box 12, Folder 310)
    - Meldon, Maurice (Issue #5), circa 1954 (Box 12, Folder 311)
    - Melo Franco, Afonso Arinos de, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 312)
    - Mendelsohn, Gloria (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 12, Folder 313)
    - Menemoncioglu, Streeter, translator, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 314)
    - Merrill, James (Issue #2), circa 1952 (Box 12, Folder 315)
    - Merton, Thomas (Issue #1), circa 1952 (Box 12, Folder 316)
    - Merwin, W. S. (William Stanley) (Issues #12 and #13), circa 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 317)
    - Michaux, Henri (Issue #15), circa 1959
      See Gregory, Patrick (Issues #12 and #15)
    - Middleton, Christopher (Issue #13), circa 1958 (Box 12, Folder 318)
    - Miller, Vassar (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 12, Folder 319)
    - Moffett, James (Issues #9, #10, and #11), circa 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 320)
    - Montale, Eugenio (Issue #2). Translated by Ben Johnson, circa 1952 (Box 12, Folder 321)
    - Montgomery, Marion (Issue #13), circa 1958 (Box 12, Folder 322)
    - Montgomery, Niall (Issue #5), circa 1954 (Box 12, Folder 323)
    - Moore, Geoffrey (Issues #8 and #10), circa 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 324-325)
    - Moore, Nicholas (Issue #7), circa 1955 (Box 12, Folder 326)
    - Moore, Rosalie (Issues #2 and #9), circa 1952, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 327)
    - Moravia, Alberto (Issue #3). Translated by Adrienne Foulk, circa 1953 (Box 13, Folder 328)
    - Morris, Herbert (Issue #3), circa 1953 (Box 13, Folder 329)
    - Morris, Wright (Issues #1 and #13), circa 1952-1958 (Box 13, Folder 330)
    - Morrison, Julia Maria (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 13, Folder 331)
    - Moss, Howard (Issues #1 and #3), circa 1953 (Box 13, Folder 332)
    - Murena, Héctor Alvarez (Issue #12), circa 1957 (Box 13, Folder 333)
      See also: De Onís, Harriet, translator (Issue #15)
    - Murray, Albert, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 334)
    - Myrivilis, Stratis (Issue #15), circa 1959 (Box 13, Folder 335)
      See also: Rick, Abbott (Issue #15)
    - Nemerov, Howard (Issues #1 and #13), circa 1958 (Box 13, Folder 336)
    - Neruda, Pablo (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 13, Folder 337)
    - Nicholson, Irene (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 13, Folder 338)
    - Niedelman, R. S. (Issue #3), circa 1953 (Box 13, Folder 339)
    - Nims, John Frederick (Issue #9), circa 1956 (Box 13, Folder 340)
    - Norse, Harold (Issue #13), circa 1958 (Box 13, Folder 341)
    - Oakes, Philip, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 342)
    - Ocampo, Silvina (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 13, Folder 343)
    - O'Connor, Flannery (Issues #1 and #8), circa 1952, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 344)
    - Ocko, Eunice (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 13, Folder 345)
    - D'Olive, Gene (Issue #12), circa 1957 (Box 13, Folder 346)
    - O'Faoláin, Seán (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 13, Folder 347)
    - Ó Faracháin, Roibeárd
      See Farren, Robert (Issue #4)
    - O'Hara, Frank (Issue #1), circa 1952 (Box 13, Folder 348)
    - Olyosha, Yuri (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 13, Folder 349)
    - Ortese, Anna Maria (Issue #5), circa 1954 (Box 13, Folder 350)
    - Osaragi, Jiro (Issue #6), circa 1954 (Box 13, Folder 351)
    - Osborn, Robert (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 13, Folder 352)
    - Pack, Robert (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 14, Folder 353)
    - Palmer, Winthrop (Issue #12), circa 1957 (Box 14, Folder 354)
    - Pamoedjo, Jesse Imam (Issue #12), circa 1957 (Box 14, Folder 355)
    - Parra, Nicanor (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 14, Folder 356)
    - Pasinetti, P. M. (Issue #1), circa 1952 (Box 14, Folder 357)
    - Pasternak, Boris Leonidovich (Issue #15), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 358)
      See also: Payne, Robert, translator (Issue #15)
    - Payne, Robert, translator (Issue #15), circa 1959 (Box 14, Folder 359)
    - Paz, Octavio (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 14, Folder 360)
    - Picasso, Pablo (Issue #2). Translated by Herma Briffault, circa 1952 (Box 14, Folder 361)
    - Pinget, Robert (Issue #3). Translated by Lionel Abel, circa 1953 (Box 14, Folder 362)
    - Piovene, Guido (Issue #4). Translated by Michael Bullock, circa 1953 (Box 14, Folder 363)
    - Pippett, Aileen (Issue #4), circa 1953 (Box 14, Folder 364)
    - Plutzik, Hyam (Issue #8), circa 1955 (Box 14, Folder 365)
    - Pollett, Elizabeth (Issue #4), circa 1953 (Box 14, Folder 366)
    - Pomeroy, Marnie (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 14, Folder 367)
    - Porter, Arabel J., 1952 (Box 14, Folder 368)
    - Prévert, Jacques (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 14, Folder 369)
    - Putman, Clay (Issue #9), circa 1956 (Box 14, Folder 370)
    - Piontek, Heinz (Issue #13), circa 1958 (Box 14, Folder 371)
    - Rainer, Dachine (Issues #11 and #12), circa 1957 (Box 14, Folder 372)
    - Rajan, B. (Issues #3 and #12), circa 1953, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 373)
    - Rattner, Abraham (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 14, Folder 374)
    - Reed, Henry (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 15, Folder 375)
    - Reeves, James (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 15, Folder 376)
    - Reid, Alastair (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 15, Folder 377)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth (Issues #9, #11, and #14), circa 1956-1958 (Box 15, Folder 378)
    - Rick, Abbott (Issue #15), circa 1959 (Box 15, Folder 379)
    - Riesman, Evelyn Thompson (Issue #9), circa 1956 (Box 15, Folder 380)
    - Riuichi, Tamura (Issue #6), circa 1954 (Box 15, Folder 381)
    - Rivers, Lucia (Issue #12), circa 1958 (Box 15, Folder 382)
    - Robinson, Edna Moore (Issue #15), circa 1959 (Box 15, Folder 383)
    - Rahe, Paul Anthony (Issues #4 and #14), circa 1953, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 384)
    - Rodman, Selden (Issue #2), circa 1952 (Box 15, Folder 385)
    - Rodman, Seldon (Issue #4)., circa 1953 (Box 15, Folder 386)
    - Rodríguez, Félix Pita (Issue #15). Translated by Harriet de Onis, circa 1959 (Box 15, Folder 387)
    - Roethke, Theodore, (Issue #2 and #4), circa 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 388)
    - Rolo, Charles J. (Issue #1), circa 1952 (Box 15, Folder 389)
    - Rossi, Jean-Baptiste (Issue #1). Translated by Adolph Gourevitch, circa 1952 (Box 15, Folder 390)
    - Rulfo, Juan (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 15, Folder 391)
    - Sabersky, Jane (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 16, Folder 392)
    - Salin, Jawad (Issue #5), circa 1954 (Box 16, Folder 393)
    - Sanson, William (Issue #4), circa 1953 (Box 16, Folder 394)
    - De Santillana, Giorgio (Issue #13), circa 1958 (Box 16, Folder 395)
    - Von Schlegell, Mary (Issue #12), circa 1957 (Box 16, Folder 396)
    - Schiller, Marvin (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 16, Folder 397)
    - Schmidt, Augusto Frederico (Issue #7), circa 1955 (Box 16, Folder 398)
    - Shorer, Mark (Issue #4), circa 1953 (Box 16, Folder 399)
    - Scott, Winfield Townley (Issues #9 and #12), circa 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 400)
    - Schuyler, James (Issue #1), circa 1952 (Box 16, Folder 401)
    - Scott, Tom (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 16, Folder 402)
    - Segre, Alfredo, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 403)
    - Seide Michael (Issue #1), circa 1952 (Box 16, Folder 404)
    - Selig, Richard (Issue #12), circa 1957 (Box 16, Folder 405)
    - Selim, Jewad, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 406)
    - Sellin, Eric (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 16, Folder 407)
    - Seymour-Smith, Martin (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 16, Folder 408)
    - Selvon, Samuel (Issue #2), circa 1952 (Box 16, Folder 409)
    - Sherman, Sarci (Issue #2), circa 1952 (Box 16, Folder 410)
      See also: Singer, Isaac Bashevis (Issue #12)
    - Shahn, Ben (Issue #4), circa 1953 (Box 16, Folder 411)
    - Shinpei, Kusano (Issue #6), circa 1954 (Box 16, Folder 412)
    - Shiro, Murano (Issue #6), circa 1954 (Box 16, Folder 413)
    - Siebel, Julia (Issue #9), circa 1956 (Box 16, Folder 414)
    - Silone, Ignazio (Issue #3). Translated by Darina Silone, circa 1953 (Box 16, Folder 415)
    - Simpson, Louis Aston Marantz (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 16, Folder 416)
    - Sinclair, Upton (Issue #8), circa 1955 (Box 16, Folder 417)
    - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (Issue #12), circa 1957 (Box 16, Folder 418)
    - Sitwell, Edith and Sacheverell, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 419)
    - Smith, Sydney Goodsir (Issue #3), circa 1953 (Box 16, Folder 420)
    - Smith, Vivian (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 16, Folder 421)
    - Smith, William Dale (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 16, Folder 422)
    - Smith, William Jay (Issues #2 and #7), circa 1952, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 423)
    - Snodgrass, W. D. (William De Witt) (Issue #1), circa 1952 (Box 16, Folder 424)
    - Solomon, Marvin (Issue #1), circa 1952 (Box 16, Folder 425)
    - Starkie, Walter (Issue #13), circa 1958 (Box 17, Folder 426)
    - Steinberg, Saul (Issues #4 and #9), circa 1953, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 427)
    - Steiner, Franz Baermann (Issue #13), circa 1958 (Box 17, Folder 428)
    - Stevens, Wallace, 1953-1957 (Box 17, Folder 429)
    - Stewart, Desmond, 1952-1957 (Box 17, Folder 430)
    - Stewart, C. Robert (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 17, Folder 431)
    - Subramanyam, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 432)
    - Summers, Hollis (Issue #3), circa 1953 (Box 17, Folder 433)
    - Swados, Harvey (Issues #2 and#12), circa 1952, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 434-435)
    - Swarthout, Glendon (Issues #5 and #13), circa 1954, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Sweeney, John L. (Issue #8), circa 1955 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Swenson, May (Issue #9), circa 1956 (Box 17, Folder 438)
    - Sylvester, William, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 439)
    - Takal, Peter (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 17, Folder 440)
    - Tambimuttu, T. (Issue #12), circa 1957 (Box 17, Folder 441)
    - Terry, J. William (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Thomas, Dylan (Issues #2 and #3), circa 1953 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Thomas, R. S. (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 17, Folder 444)
    - Tommaney, J. J. (Issue #8), circa 1955 (Box 17, Folder 445)
    - Torri, Julio (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 17, Folder 446)
    - Toyotaro, Kizo (Issue #6), circa 1954 (Box 17, Folder 447)
    - Trieted, Ralph (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 17, Folder 448)
    - Trimpi, Wesley (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 17, Folder 449)
    - Trocchi, Alexander (Issue #3), circa 1953 (Box 17, Folder 450)
    - Tunnard, Christopher and Henry Hope Reed (Issue #3), circa 1953 (Box 17, Folder 451)
    - Uhr, Leonard Merrick (Issue #5), circa 1954 (Box 18, Folder 452)
    - Vaid, Krishna Baldev (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 18, Folder 453)
    - Van Doren, Mark, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 454)
    - Vazakas, Byron (Issue #3), circa 1953 (Box 18, Folder 455)
    - Vennberg, Karl (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 18, Folder 456)
    - Tarjei Vesaas (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 18, Folder 457)
    - Vierreck, Peter (Issue #2), circa 1952 (Box 18, Folder 458)
    - Villaurrutia, Xavier (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 18, Folder 459)
    - Vittorini (Issue #9), circa 1956 (Box 18, Folder 460)
    - Vowles, Richard B. (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 18, Folder 461)
    - Vidal, Gore (Issues #1, #4, and #10), circa 1952-1956 (Box 18, Folder 462)
    - Wain, John (Issues #6 and #12), circa 1954-1957 (Box 18, Folder 463)
    - Wagner, Geoffrey Atheling (Issue #15), circa 1959 (Box 18, Folder 464)
    - Wagoner, David (Issues #4 and #9), circa 1953-1956 (Box 18, Folder 465)
    - Walcott, Derek (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 18, Folder 466)
    - Wakefield, Dan (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 18, Folder 467)
    - Watkins, Vernon Phillips (Issue #5), circa 1954 (Box 18, Folder 468)
    - Weales, Gerald Clifford (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 18, Folder 469)
    - Webber, Gordon (Issue #6), circa 1954 (Box 18, Folder 470)
    - Weinstack, Herbert (Issue #9), circa 1956 (Box 18, Folder 471)
    - Weiss, Neil (Issue #12), circa 1957 (Box 18, Folder 472)
    - Weiss, T. (Thomas Norbert) (Issue #9), circa 1956 (Box 18, Folder 473)
    - Weldon, John Lee (Issue #3), circa 1953 (Box 18, Folder 474)
    - West, Anthony (Issue #11), circa 1957 (Box 18, Folder 475)
    - West, John Anthony (Issue #13), circa 1958 (Box 18, Folder 476)
    - West, Paul (Issue #13), circa 1958 (Box 18, Folder 477)
    - Westphalen, Emilio Adolfo (Issue #14), circa 1958 (Box 18, Folder 478)
    - Whatmough, Joshua, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 479)
    - Whittemore, Reed (Issue #13), circa 1958 (Box 19, Folder 480)
    - Wierzynski, Casimir (Issue #2), circa 1952 (Box 19, Folder 481)
    - Wilbur, Richard (Issues #5 and #8), circa 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 482)
    - Wilkins, Eithne (Mrs. Ernst Kaiser) (Issue #8), circa 1955 (Box 19, Folder 483)
    - Williams, Tennessee (Issue #1), circa 1952 (Box 19, Folder 484)
    - Williams, Williams Carlos (Issues #5 and #8), circa 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 485)
    - Willington, Calder (Issue #2), circa 1952 (Box 19, Folder 486)
    - Worth, Valerie (Issue #7), circa 1955 (Box 19, Folder 487)
    - Wright, James (Issue #9), circa 1956 (Box 19, Folder 488)
    - Wysong, Robert John (Issue #10), circa 1956 (Box 19, Folder 489)
    - Yasuo, Fujitomi, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 490)
    - Yeats, William Butler, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 491)
    - Young, Marguerite (Issue #6), circa 1954 (Box 19, Folder 492)
    - Young, Vernon (Issue #4), circa 1953 (Box 19, Folder 493)
    - Zafar, Sirajuddin (Issue #2), circa 1952 (Box 19, Folder 494)
    - Zekowski, Arlene (Issue #11), circa 1957
      See Berne, Stanley (Issue #11)
  - Agent and Publisher Correspondence, 1952-1960
    - "A-E" General, circa 1952-1959 (Box 20, Folder 495)
    - "F-K" General, circa 1952-1959 (Box 20, Folder 496)
    - "L-M" General, circa 1952-1959 (Box 20, Folder 497)
    - "N-R" General, circa 1952-1959 (Box 20, Folder 498)
    - "S-Z" General, circa 1952-1959 (Box 20, Folder 499)
    - Brandt & Brandt, 1952-1957 (Box 20, Folder 500)
    - Brown, James O., 1952-1960 (Box 20, Folder 501)
    - Curis Brown, LTD., 1952-1958 (Box 20, Folder 502)
    - Klausner, Bertha, International Literary Agent, 1952-1958 (Box 20, Folder 503)
    - MCA Management, Ltd., 1952-1958 (Box 21, Folder 504)
    - Monica McCall, Inc., 1952-1958 (Box 21, Folder 505)
    - McCrindle, J. F., 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 506)
    - McIntosh McKee, 1952-1959 (Box 21, Folder 507)
    - Porcelain, Sidney E., Author's Representative, 1952-1958 (Box 21, Folder 508)
    - Rodell, Marie F. (Marie Freid), Author's Representative, 1952-1955 (Box 21, Folder 509)
    - Russell and Vokening, 1952-1958 (Box 21, Folder 510)
    - Schaffner, John, Literary Agent, 1952-1959 (Box 21, Folder 511)
    - William Morris Agency, 1952-1959 (Box 21, Folder 512)
    - Wolf, Harriet, 1952-1955 (Box 21, Folder 513)
- Manuscripts, 1952-1959; Series II; 5.4; (13 boxes)
  Arranged alphabetically by author's name. Miscellaneous manuscripts are arranged by issue at the end of the series.
  Series II, Manuscripts, consists of typescripts of works published in New World Writing, corrected for publication. Also found are some original drawings.
  - Abse, Dannie. "Emperors of the Island", undated (Box 22, Folder 514)
  - Achterberg, Gerrit. "The Black Spring", undated (Box 22, Folder 515)
  - Adamov, Arthur. "Professor Taranne", undated (Box 22, Folder 516)
  - Agbadja, Adolph. "Heaven Is a Fine Place", undated (Box 22, Folder 517)
  - Aichinger, Ilse. "Angel in the Night", undated (Box 22, Folder 518)
  - Aldridge, John W. "P.G. Wodehouse: The Lesson of the young Master", undated (Box 22, Folder 519)
  - Alexander, A. J. "To Build a House", undated (Box 22, Folder 520)
  - Algren, Nelson. "Beasts of the Wild", undated (Box 22, Folder 521)
  - Allen, Gay Wilson. "Walt Whitman: 'Cosmos-Inspired'", undated (Box 22, Folder 522)
  - Allen, Gregory. "Of Death, Of Life", undated (Box 22, Folder 523)
  - Allen, Walter. "The Review in America", undated (Box 22, Folder 524)
  - Alvarez, Alfred. "The Catharsis", undated (Box 22, Folder 525)
  - Alvaro, Corrado. "The Hero in Crisis", undated (Box 22, Folder 526)
  - Amaral, José Vázquez. "New Writing from Latin America", undated (Box 22, Folder 527)
  - Amen, Grover. "Under a Normal Noon...", undated (Box 22, Folder 528)
  - Anderson, Patrick. "Miss Grier", undated (Box 22, Folder 529)
  - Antonov, Sergei. "Application Form", undated (Box 22, Folder 530)
  - Armstrong, Louis. "Storyville Days and Nights", undated (Box 22, Folder 531)
  - Arnér, Sivar. "The Osprey and the Pike", undated (Box 22, Folder 532)
  - Arreola, Juan Jose. "The Rhinoceros", undated (Box 22, Folder 533)
  - Ashberry, John. "He", undated (Box 22, Folder 534)
  - Atik, Leah. "Jochebed's Lullaby", undated (Box 22, Folder 535)
  - Auchincloss, Louis
    - "Billy and the Gargoyles", undated (Box 22, Folder 536)
    - "The Gem-Like Flame", undated (Box 22, Folder 537)
  - Auden, W. H. (Wystan Hugh). "Some Notes on Grimm and Anderson.", undated (Box 22, Folder 538)
  - Baldwin, James. "Roy's Wound", undated (Box 22, Folder 539)
  - Ball, Everett. "A Painting for Isolde", undated (Box 22, Folder 540)
  - Bandeira, Manuel
    - "Boarding House", undated (Box 22, Folder 541)
    - "Moment in a Cafe", undated (Box 22, Folder 542)
  - Barker, George. "In the Shade of the Old Apple Tree", undated (Box 22, Folder 543)
  - Baro, Gene. "Bereavement", undated (Box 22, Folder 544)
  - Bayley, John Barrington. Drawings, undated (Box 22, Folder 545)
  - Beckett, Samuel
    - "Molloy", undated (Box 22, Folder 546)
    - "Yellow", undated (Box 22, Folder 547)
  - Bell, Charles G.
    - "The Fall of Candida", undated (Box 22, Folder 548)
    - "The Fall of Troy", undated (Box 22, Folder 549)
  - Bellow, Saul
    - "Distractions of a Fiction Writer", undated (Box 22, Folder 550)
    - "The Wrecker", undated (Box 22, Folder 551)
  - Benn, Gottfried. "People Met", undated (Box 22, Folder 552)
  - Bennet, Peggy
    - "The Bronco-Buster", undated (Box 22, Folder 553)
    - "Over the Green Sands", undated (Box 22, Folder 554)
  - Bentley, Nelson
    - "Atget's Lens", undated (Box 22, Folder 555)
    - "Villanelle", undated (Box 22, Folder 556)
  - Berger, Thomas. "Confession of a Giant", undated (Box 22, Folder 557)
  - Berriault, Gina. "Something in His Nature", undated (Box 22, Folder 558)
  - Berto, Guiseppe. "The Seed Among Thorns", undated (Box 22, Folder 559)
  - Bey, Hamdi. "The Indian Intelligentsia and the Western World", undated (Box 22, Folder 560)
  - Bishop, Elizabeth. "Exchanging Hats", undated (Box 23, Folder 561)
  - Bishop, Leonard. "The Substance of Siody", undated (Box 23, Folder 562)
  - Blazer, Samuel. "Chicheuache, the Human-Cow", undated (Box 23, Folder 563)
  - Bloom, Robert. "The Mare in the Hayloft", undated (Box 23, Folder 564)
  - Bly, Robert
    - "Admiral Brown", undated (Box 23, Folder 565)
    - "America is Dancing", undated (Box 23, Folder 566)
    - "The Ascension of J. D. Morgan", undated (Box 23, Folder 567)
    - "Each Day I Live", undated (Box 23, Folder 568)
    - "For Three American Heroes", undated (Box 23, Folder 569)
    - "Gloria Dei Lutheran Church", undated (Box 23, Folder 570)
    - "MacDougal Street, New York", undated (Box 23, Folder 571)
    - "Mr. McElroy", undated (Box 23, Folder 572)
    - "None of Us Are Innocent", undated (Box 23, Folder 573)
    - "Proclamation", undated (Box 23, Folder 574)
    - "Remembering in Oslo the Old Picture of the Magna Charta", undated (Box 23, Folder 575)
    - "The Search Back Through Memory", undated (Box 23, Folder 576)
    - "Since His Course Must be Right", undated (Box 23, Folder 577)
    - "Thinking of Wallace Stevens on the First Snowy Day in December", undated (Box 23, Folder 578)
    - "Warning to the Reader", undated (Box 23, Folder 579)
    - "We Have Overlooked Something", undated (Box 23, Folder 580)
    - "The Westerns", undated (Box 23, Folder 581)
    - "What Burns and Is Consumed", undated (Box 23, Folder 582)
  - Bluestone, George. "A Semblance of Compassion", undated (Box 23, Folder 583)
  - Bolland, Patrick. "Trials of a Poet", undated (Box 23, Folder 584)
  - Boll, Heinrich. "My Expensive Leg", undated (Box 23, Folder 585)
  - Booth, Phillip
    - "Fourteen Student Poets", undated (Box 23, Folder 586)
    - "Twelfth Night", undated (Box 23, Folder 587)
  - Borges, Jorge Luis
    - "Deutsches Requiem", undated (Box 23, Folder 588)
    - "The Share of the Sword", undated (Box 23, Folder 589)
  - Bosch, Juan. "The Beautiful Soul of Don Danian", undated (Box 23, Folder 590)
  - Bosquet, Alain. "Two Poems", undated (Box 23, Folder 591)
  - Branner, H. C. (Hans Christian). "Morning", undated (Box 23, Folder 592)
  - Brecht, Bertolt. "On Watering the Garden", undated (Box 23, Folder 593)
  - Breit, Harvey. "Turks and Madonnas", undated (Box 23, Folder 594)
  - Brew, O. H. Kwesi. "Ancestral Faces", undated (Box 23, Folder 595)
  - Brinnin, John Malcolm
    - "Carmarthen Bar", undated (Box 23, Folder 596)
    - "Modern American Poetry", undated (Box 23, Folder 597)
  - Brockway, Wallace. "The Nobel Literary Prize: A Long View", undated (Box 23, Folder 598)
  - Brower, Brock. "The Tender Edge", undated (Box 23, Folder 599)
  - Brown, Spencer. "Candlemas Near a Parkway", undated (Box 23, Folder 600)
  - Broyard, Anatole. "For He's a Jolly Good Fellow", undated (Box 23, Folder 601)
  - Brunson, Beverly. "A Bastard of the Blood", undated (Box 23, Folder 602)
  - Budlong, Paula. "A Season in Algona Illinois", undated (Box 23, Folder 603)
  - Burr, Gray. "The Wealth of Hills", undated (Box 23, Folder 604)
  - Busta, Christine. "Show at Advent", undated (Box 23, Folder 605)
  - Butler, Clare McGrath
    - "The Exchange", undated (Box 23, Folder 606)
    - "Who Lives Alas Away", undated (Box 23, Folder 607)
  - Butler, Guy. "Cape Coloured Batman", undated (Box 23, Folder 608)
  - Caldwell, Erskine. "How to Live Like an Author", undated (Box 23, Folder 609)
  - Calisher, Hortense. "The Rehabilitation of Ginerva Leake", undated (Box 23, Folder 610)
  - Candido, Anthony N. "Five Drawings", undated (Box 23, Folder 611)
  - Cantwell, Robert. "The Faulkners: Recollections of a Gifted Family", undated (Box 23, Folder 612)
  - Carpentier, Alejo. "The Lost Steps", undated (Box 23, Folder 613)
  - Carreño, José Suárez. "Evenings in Madrid", undated (Box 23, Folder 614)
  - Carunugan, Celso Al. "Like a Big Brave Man", undated (Box 23, Folder 615)